# Antonio Marks

Cell |443-875-5824 |

Email | marksantonio12@gmail.com |
Github Profile | https://github.com/tonemarks |
Website | https://tonemarks.github.io |

# **PROFILE**

Reliable and motivated with 5 years customer service, management, and mentoring experience.

Previously enrolled in the allied health trade program which taught the basics of healthcare and human services. Completed the JHU data science course set in September 2018.

# **EDUCATION & TRAINING**

#### JHU Chromebook Data Science

Leanpub | 2018

Online training with courses involving:

- R Programming
- Data Visualization
- Data Analysis
- Data Wrangling

## **High School**

Mergenthaler Vocational-Technical High School |2018

Vocational Training - Allied Health & Human Services which included modules involving:

- Customer service
- Specialized coursework on:
  - Biological Sciences
  - Anatomy

## **Certificate of Completion**

Morgan State University | 2012, 2013

A hands-on experience (Science Engineering Mathematics and Aerospace Academy \*SEMAA\*) aligned to the National Math, Science, and Technology standards with a curriculum involving:

- Science
- Technology
- Engineering
- Mathematics (or STEM)

## Technology

- 1. Microsoft Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint, etc.
- 2. Google Drive, Docs, Slides, etc.
- 3. R Programming
- 4. R Markdown (.Rmd)

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Yo Baltimore HEBCAC

Volunteer Tutor | 02 / 2018 to 04 / 2018

Asked to volunteer as tutor for a couple of students at YO! Baltimore eastside.

## **Five Below**

Holiday Sales Associate | 12 / 2017 to 1 / 2018

Seasonal retail position where I was responsible for stocking the store and directing customers to help as they shopped.

#### **Urban BBQ**

Head Cashier/Front of House Manager | 06 / 2017 to 10 / 2017

Food service position where I was responsible for the whole front half of the store (Hiring, customer service, cleaning, open/closing, etc.)

## Ledo's Pizza

Cashier | 06 / 2017 to 10 / 2017

Food service position where I was responsible for customer service and serving customers their food.

## **Baltimore City Department of Transportation**

Intern | 06 / 2015 to 08 / 2015

YouthWorks position in which I had to replace and update Transportation Department signs throughout Baltimore City.